I think you should be aiming for 20% of
the people who follow you to be on your
email list.
I have about 450,000 on mine at the
moment, and that's just for
one of my businesses. Collectively,
I have about 600,000 emails,
and I know that's
technically just over 10% of my following.
But for your smaller accounts, 20%
is the benchmark.
And if you said, "James,
you can lose your social media accounts
or your email
list," I'd keep the email list.
It's way more sacred, and this
is something I'll
teach you across time on this channel.
There are loads of ways to grow your email
list.
One of the ways is I like to cleverly link
a link in the description offering
something like, I don't know,
30 mind-blowing nuggets of wisdom to help
your brand
and business for free, which
are cleverly delivered at the same time
every day.
So check that out at the end of this
video.
And do it, just literally copy me,
because by the end of that automation,
you'll
resonate with the emotional journey
necessary to compel people to want to
consider
to do business with you